你看到镜子里的那人了吗?
Did you see the guy in the viewing room?
没有
No
是爸爸
It was Dad.
我认识这家伙
I know that guy.
是什么?
What is it?
这是嵌在迈克尔·斯科菲尔德皮肉里的纤维
It was fused into Michael Scofield's skin.
从哪来的?
Where'd it come from?
依我看 是狱警制服上的
As far as I can tell, a guard's uniform.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
监狱的蓝图
The blueprints,
从精神病区通往医务室的那部分
the ones we need to get from the psych ward to the infirmary,
不见了
they're gone.
嘿 看起来不错呵
Hey, that's looking good.
还真挺有进展
You're making some real progress.
石灰泥增加了重量
The plaster adds a lot of weight.
我也许得加固下
I may have to add reinforcements.
怎样都行 只要能赶上我的婚礼纪念日
Whatever it takes, as long as you get done in time for the anniversary.
我会完成的. 拿住这个
It'll be done. Hold this.
你知道 伊朗王十分喜爱泰姬陵
You know, the Shah loved his Taj so much
因此他在河对岸又造了一个一模一样的庙宇
that he built another temple just like it on the other side of the river.
几乎完全一样
It was an absolute mirror image.
只是黑了一点 可以说是"黑色泰姬陵"
Except it was darker, it was like a black Taj Mahal.
从没听说过
Never heard of it.
那是因为这工程从未完工
Well, that's 'cause it was never completed.
在他完工之前 他的政权被他最爱的儿子推翻了
He was overthrown by his favorite son before he could finish it.
-听起来像个神话故事似的  -不 这100%是真的
-Sounds like a myth.  -No, it's 100% true.
我觉得是
I think.
打扰一下 狱长 医生要见你
Excuse me, Warden. Dr. Tancredi is here to see you.
谢谢
Thank you.
亚当 带斯科菲尔德先生 回牢房去吧
Adams, please escort Mr. Scofield back to his cell.
医生 有什么需要我效劳的吗?
Doctor, what can I do for you?
其实是和斯科菲尔德有关的 长官
Actually, it's about Scofield, sir.
进去谈
Come in.
斯科菲尔德怎么了?
What about Scofield?
他的背部被烫得相当的严重
The burn on his back is fairly serious.
他看上去恢复的不错
He seems to be recovering.
起先我以为他是被另一个囚犯所伤
At first, I assumed he was being assaulted by another inmate,
但我在他的皮肤里面发现这个
but I found this embedded in the skin on his back.
这是什么?
What's this?
是纤维
It's fabric.
狱警制服上的
Came from a guard's uniform.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我试着回忆那些丢失的通道...
I'm trying to remember those blueprints,
那些被烫掉的部分
what we lost to the burn.
没有那部分 我们绝不可能通得过 精神病区的地下管道
Without them, we'll never be able to navigate those pipes beneath psych ward.
-现在如何?  -不行
-Any luck?  -No.
我曾花了很长时间研究整张设计图...
I spent a lot of time studying those blueprints,
没日没夜的研究
tracing them night after night,
思考每一条可能通往医务室的路线
considering every possible route to the infirmary.
这感觉就像是对你10年前学的东西 再来一次测验一样
It's like trying to take a test you studied for 10 years ago.
P.I.(狱工)!
P.I.
真不知道怎么给他们搞成那样
How do they get like that, I got no idea.
我知道 扯过的口袋太多了
I do. Tugging on too many pockets.
她扯过你的口袋了??
She tug on your pocket?
我爱好交际 但我还是个有底线的人
I may be social, but that's the boundary line even I won't cross.
怎么样了? 什么时候能行动?
So how about it, Fish? When we rolling out?
还差一点 我已经在着手了
One hiccup left, but I'm working on it.
是吗 还差什么?
Yeah, and what is that?
我们的路线还不是太完善
Our road map's a little incomplete at the moment.
我不明白 为什么不再下去看看?
I don't get it. Why not just go down there again?
因为 第一: 我没有狱警服了
'Cause, one, I don't have the guard's uniform anymore,
就是说我没办法穿过院子 或者说后勤室
which means I can't get across the yard or past the orderly.
第二: 即使我去成了 那里也是一团糟
And two, even if I did, it's a mess down there.
我需要这个
I need this.
你觉得你能记起来吗?
You think you're gonna remember it?
你不要催我就行
Not with you hounding me.
收工了 外面要开始大扫除
Time to wrap it up. We're going to have you start exterminating.
这边还没完工呢
We're not done in here.
我看是差不多了
Well, you look done to me.
没呢 地毯什么的都还没动过
No, CO, we still got the carpet to do, man.
不用了 贝利克会叫专业人员来做
No, Bellick is going to bring professionals in to do that.
他想把工作做得好点
Wants the job done right.
-他们什么时候来?  -明天
-When's that going to happen?  -Tomorrow.
这下我们惹上大麻烦了 不是吗?
We got a real problem on our hands, don't we?
那帮家伙一进来
Rug monkeys gonna come in here,
掀开地毯 那个洞就会喜迎他们的到来
tear up that carpet and that hole's gonna be smiling up at them.
-我们得把它填上  -我们才刚刚挖好
-We'll have to fill it in.  -We just dug that bitch.
我们只需要一块夹板
All we need is a piece of plywood
然后在上面涂上几英寸厚的速干混凝土
and a couple inches of that fast-setting concrete on top of it.
铺地毯的人发现不了这个洞的
The carpet guys will never know there's anything beneath it.
如果我们要出去
And the night we break out,
只需用个大锤子砸碎它就行了
we'll just smash through with a sledgehammer.
好了 干活吧
Well, okay. Let's get on it.
我们只剩下几个小时的时间了
We've only got a couple hours to get this thing done.
嘿 颓纳 见过艾弗卡托吗?
Hey, Tweener. You met Avocado?
嘿 别来无恙啊?
Yo, what's up?
瞧 她还是个孩子
Lookit. She's just a baby.
走吧
Hit road.
坐
Have a seat.
那么...
So...
斯科菲尔德那边有什么消息不?
Scofield. What's the 911?
没什么 我真不太清楚 我不常和他们呆一块儿
It's 411, and I don't know, man. I ain't up in his car.
知道吗 艾弗卡托要找个新狱友
You know, Avocado's looking for a new cellie.
老大 拜托 我想和他们套近乎
Boss, come on, man, I'm trying to break bread with the man,
但我接近不了他们 除非我和他们一块儿干活
but I can't get jack unless I can get to the table.
知道我的意思吗?
You know what I'm saying?
斯科菲尔德那帮家伙全在P.I里面 他不需要我
Scofield got his own peeps up in PI. He don't need me.
这东西多久会干?
How long this stuff take to dry?
一 二个小时
One, two hours.
警报
Fire on the line.
这地方好啊 我听说这里要装卫星电视
This place is sweet. I heard we're getting satellite.
可以看很多A片了 老大
Yeah, all the porn you can watch, boss.
不错 不错
Good, good.
你们的活干的很漂亮
You know, you girls
我想再来个帮手应该会更好
I thought you could use an extra pair of hands on the crew.
好啊?!
What's up?
嘿 伙计们 看我这把刷子 都粘在一块儿了
Hey, man, look at my brush. It's all sticking together.
得派个人出去把这个弄干净
Somebody needs to go clean them out.
论资格 应该是 你了
According to rank, that would be you.
我该怎么做?
What do I gotta do?
院子里有水管 你用那个吧
There's a hose out by the shed in the yard. You can use that.
也把这些弄干净了
Clean those, too.
好吧
All right.
抱歉搞杂了你们的聚会
Sorry I busted up the party, yo.
他是谁?
Who is he?
你只需知道
For your purposes, all you need to know
照片中的这家伙曾经也为这家公司卖力 后来变得吊儿郎当
is that man in the photo used to work for the Company. He went rogue.
他怎么卷进来的?
And how's he involved in this situation?
他是布伦斯的父亲
He's Burrows' father.
等 等 等
Wait, wait, wait.
你挑了个公司里人的儿子做替罪羊?
You picked the son of a Company man to be our patsy?
公司知道吗?
Did the Company know?
公司知道 就这些
The Company did know. That was the whole point.
你能不能帮忙解释一下?
How about you elaborate on that?
你能不能不要问这些问题?
How about you stop with all the questions?
你是个挺不错的保镖 就这样
You are a glorified bodyguard, that's it.
你的工作是被人看到 而不是被人听到 明白了吗?
Your job's to be seen, not to be heard. Is that understood?
-好了吗?  -哦 差不多快好了
-How close are we?  -Oh, we're good to go, baby.
-又有人来了  -这是怎么了 狂欢派队?
-Got another badge.  -What is this, happy hour?
斯科菲尔德? 狱长要见你
Scofield? Pope wants to see you.
其他人收工 这里到此为止
The rest of you round up, you're done in here.
嘿 帕特森狱警说我们要干到天黑
Hey, CO Patterson said we had till the end of the day to finish up.
我说你们可以走了
And I say you're done.
太阳下山前 院子里的有些活你们必须完成
There's a couple hours of work I want done in the yard before sundown.
快 行动
Come on, let's go.
-我们死定了  -还没有
-We're dead.  -We're not.
-我会搞定的  -今晚必须弄好
-I'll get it done.  -It's gotta be done tonight.
我说了我会搞定的
I said I'll get it done.
斯科菲尔德 监狱长在等你
Scofield, Pope's waiting.
嘿 林肯
Hey, Linc.
让我出去吗?
You going to let me out?
不 林肯 我是来告诉你 他们又定了日期
No, Linc, just came to let you know they set a new date.
检察院重新查看了所有文件
DOC refiled all the paperwork.
行刑日为下周5的凌晨
Execution's a week from Friday at midnight.
能让我去院子里走走吗?
You going to let me out in the yard or what?
除非狱长下命令 否则我没这个权力 抱歉
Unless I hear it from the Pope himself, I can't do it. I'm sorry.
拜托了 老兄 就10分钟 我只要求10分钟
Come on, man, 10 minutes. That's all I'm asking. Ten minutes.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
某个家伙走进法院
Some guy just walks into the courtroom,
扔下一些医学纪录 林肯就获得了缓期执行
drops off some medical records, Lincoln gets a stay of execution,
然后他就这么消失了
then "poof," he disappears into the cold.
你觉得可能是谁 某个狂热的死刑反对分子?
Who do you think it could be, some anti-death penalty fanatic?
别傻了 这不可能
Oh, come on, in this case, I doubt it.
没有名字 也没有文档 我们根本无从查起
But without a name or a paper trail, we got no way of getting to him.
所以说我们一无所获了
So once again we have nothing.
能得到两个礼拜的缓期 不能说是一无所获吧?
I wouldn't exactly call a two-week stay nothing, okay?
情况至少比昨天要好
It's more than we had yesterday.
能问你个问题吗?
Can I ask you a question?
你是否真的认为 我们能查个水落石出?
Do you really think that you're going to get to the bottom of this?
或者他们会让我们查个水落石出?
That they'll let you get to the bottom of this?
这些人并不存在
These guys don't exist.
你用法律对付他们 他们会反过来用它来对付你
You go after them with the law, and they'll just use it against you.
我们尽最大的努力 好吗?
We're doing the best we can, okay?
法律是将他们绳之以法的唯一手段 LJ
Law's the only way we're going to bring them to justice, LJ.
他们枪杀了我母亲
They gunned my mother down, man.
你觉得还有什么公正不公正?
You think I give a damn about justice?
我要他们死 以其人之道还其人之身
I want them. I wanna do to them what they did to me.
行了 LJ
Come on, LJ.
这是由法院决定的 不是我们
It's for the courts to decide, not us.
听着 他们总会有疏忽的时候
Look, they're going to slip up, okay?
总有些证据是他们驳不倒的
They're going to leave a piece of evidence that can't be refuted.
会有机会让我们抓住这些证据的
And we're going to be waiting to nail them when they do.
或许他们已经疏忽大意了
Maybe they already slipped up.
小屋边 井里面
Up at the cabin, at the well.
魁恩
Quinn.
被人盖上了
Somebody covered it up.
一定是有人把他救走了
They must have come and gotten him.
揭开再下定论
There's only one way to find out.
看 他的手机
Look, there's his cell phone.
慢点
Easy.
好 再低一点 再低一点
Okay, a little lower!
好 我拿到了
Okay, I got it.
你没事吧?
You okay?
是的 我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
拉我上去
Pull me up.
我想和他单独谈谈 加里?
Would you give us a minute, Gary?
迈克尔 我要你绝对诚实
Michael, I want you to be absolutely honest with me.
唐克雷蒂医生发现 这东西嵌在你的皮肤里面
Dr. Tancredi found this embedded in your flesh when she was treating you.
显然 这是狱警制服上面的
Apparently, it came from a guard's uniform.
你是不是被哪位警卫打了?
Have you been assaulted by an officer?
迈克尔 迈克尔 我要你回答
Michael, Michael, I need an answer.
这不再是一个坚守狱友准则的问题了
This is not about sticking to the inmates' code anymore.
这是一个警卫的行为检点问题 是我的责任
This is about officer misconduct. That's my responsibility.
你不想看到我丢饭碗 不是吗?
You wouldn't want to see me lose my job now, would you?
不 当然不想
o, of course not.
你对我和哥哥都很不错
You have been very good to me and my brother.
那我得知道你怎么会被烫伤的 现在
Then I need to know where you got that burn. Right now.
否则 你将被单独禁闭 明白吗?
Otherwise, your ass is going to solitary. You understand?
随你选
It's your choice.
-听我说  -冷静点!
-Don't... Hey, please, listen to me.  -Cool down!
听我说 别这么做! 别这么做!
Listen to me, don't do this! don't do this!
迈克尔!
Michael!
不!
No!
迈克尔
Michael?
迈克尔? 迈克尔?
Michael? Michael?
林肯?
Linc?
你怎么会在这儿的?
What the hell are you doing in here?
林肯 我们惹上大麻烦了
Linc, we're in a lot of trouble now.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
狱长问了我些问题 我很难回答
The Pope asked some questions that I couldn't answer.
关于什么的?
About what?
他有证据证明 我出现在我不应该出现的地方
He's got proof that I was where I wasn't supposed to be.
他还不知道
He doesn't know it,
他迟早会搞清楚整件事情的来龙去脉的
but sooner or later he's going to put the whole thing together.
没办法了
There's no way out of this.
不 有办法的 你一定要有信念
Yeah, there is. You just got to keep the faith.
不
No.
我倾注了所有心血  结果却功亏一篑
I put my blood into this, and it's coming apart.
听我说
Listen to me.
禁闭的目的就是要搞垮你
The whole point of solitary is to break you,make you crazy.
你必须学会坚强 听到了吗?
You got to keep strong, you hear me?
别让他们击垮你
Don't let them break you.
我倾注了所有心血
I put my blood into this.
宝贝 很抱歉我现在才联系你
Look, baby, I'm so sorry it took me so long to get back to you.
搞了半天我们师近日不会被调离了
Turns out that our division is not getting mobilized for a couple more days.
收不到你的消息 我真的不知所措
When I didn't hear from you, I didn't know what to think, baby.
我好担心 不停的看新闻 注意伤亡人员的名单
I got so worried. I started watching the news, looking for casualties.
我很对不起 但你要相信
I'm so sorry about all this. You gotta believe that.
我打电话给后遣分队办公室
I started calling the rear detachment office,
询问117分队是否出了什么事
asking if there was some sort of problem with the 117th.
没有 117分队没出任何问题
No. There's not a problem with the 117th.
我们快回来了 这里的情况 就是有点乱七八糟 就这些
We're coming back. It's a snafu, that's all.
再几天我们就可以回来了 宝贝儿
A couple more days, and we'll be on those hops, baby.
可后遣分队的长官不是这么说的
That's not what the rear detachment officer said.
他说117分队要6个月后才能回来
He said the 117th wasn't coming home for another six months.
什么? 哦 不 那不可能
What? No. That can't be right.
-他就是这么说的  -啊 你知道为什么吗?
-That's what he said.  -You know what it is?
是由于调度的原因
It's because we're transpo.
你知道 严格讲 我们队是从140师分遣出来的
You know, technically we're on a loan-out from the 140th.
所以他才那么说
I mean, that's why he said that.
-140师?  -是的 是
-The 140th?  -Yeah, yeah.
只要再几天就行了 我是说...
It's just a few more days. That's all. I mean,
你没必要打那些电话 我会回来的 好吗?
you don't need to go calling anyone. I'll be back, okay?
我一知道确切日期就马上告诉你
I will call you as soon as I know the exact date.
-好吗? 我爱你  -我爱你
-Okay? I love you.-I love you.
迈克尔被关单独禁闭了
Michael's in the SHU.
哦 天 这坏事是一个接一个
Oh, God, the hits just keep coming!
伙计们 不到最后就不要慌张
Last thing we wanna do now is panic, fellas.
现在足以让人慌张的了 老头
Oh, it's panic time, old head.
房间里的那个洞还没完工
We got an unfinished hole in that room over there
斯科菲尔德本应该晚上去把它搞定的
that Scofield was supposed to fill tonight.
明早8:00点 他们一揭开毯子 我们就玩完了
Come tomorrow 8: 00 a.m., they rip up that carpet, our game is over.
除非谁把它填好
Unless someone else fills it.
没错 你是唯一一个能从水槽后通向外面的
That's right, papi.You're the only one with a toilet open to the outside world.
你是说让我今晚一个人过去?
You're saying I go out there by myself tonight?
我们就是这个意思
That's exactly what we're saying.
开什么玩笑? 那不可能
Are you kidding? That's impossible.
我现在不想听你说"不可能"
Look, I don't wanna hear impossible from you right now!
还有个人在等着我
I got people waiting on me,
一个我可能会失去的人 除非你让我赶快从这儿出去
people that I'm gonna lose, unless you man up and get some cojones, comprende?
你说起来容易 命悬一线的不是你
That's easy for you to say, pendejo. It ain't your ass on the line.
我们所有人都命在悬梁
All of our asses are on the line.
现在只有你能为大伙做点什么
And you're the only cat that can do something about it.
是啊 也许我能走出我的牢房
Yeah, maybe I can get out of my cell.
也许我能进到警卫室
And maybe I can get into the guards' room.
但如果我那么做了 且把洞填平了
But even if I do, and I fill that hole in,
我仍会在那个房间
I'll still be in that room.
已经被封住了 你叫我怎么出去
I'll be sealed in. There's no way out.
斯科菲尔德一定还有其他路线
Scofield must've had a way.
他确实有
He did.
上次他走过的那条壁炉路线
The grate at the sally port.
哦 对?开阔地中央的那个洞
Oh, that's right. The one out there in the middle of the open?
是啊 你最好准备好 伙计
Yeah, so you better lace up, amigo,
因为你可能得跑着去洞那边
'cause you're gonna have to make a run for it.
如果我被抓住 那可是一个10年徒刑啊
That's 10 years on my bid if I get caught.
所以最好想办法不要被抓住
Then you better figure out a way not to get caught.
列队!
Line it up!
今晚 伙计 只能是今晚
Tonight, primo. It's gotta be tonight.
迈克尔
Michael.
你没事吧?你在干什么?
You okay? What you doing?
试着回想精神病区下面的构架
I'm trying to remember what's beneath psych ward.
你不应该想这个问题
You're thinking about the wrong thing.
你应该想如何从这个禁闭出去
You got to think about how to get out of here.
迈克尔
Michael.
来 跟我说说话
Man, come on. Talk to me.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
你们要我干那事 你也总得为我做点事儿
If I'm gonna be the one doing that running, you gotta do some lifting, too.
你知道你在要求我干什么吗?
I mean, you know what you're asking of me?
你在为全队效力
You gotta do it for the team.
嘿 老妹 你那花短裤露出来了
Hey, sister. Your bloomers are showing.
哦 宝贝 不是露出来 是骄傲地飞出来
They aren't showing, baby, they're flying. Proudly.
我就把你当成是一派对女孩了
I take it you are a party girl.
L.J.? 快 我们走了
LJ? Come on, we're leaving.
好
Okay.
只要能把魁恩的手机换个电源 里面的信息肯定很宝贵
We get Quinn's phone powered up and it could be a gold mine of information.
不对 对不上
No. Doesn't fit.
能找到一块合适的充电器就行
We just need to find the right adapter.
魁恩怎么办? 我们就把他丢在这儿?
What about Quinn? Are we just gonna leave him here?
那个从后面开枪打我的家伙?
You mean the guy who shot me in the back?
对 我们就把他留在这儿
Yeah, we're just gonna leave him here.
你若敢告诉别人 我就...
You tell anyone about this, and I...
今早在国会大厦的辩论第一次陷入僵局
Capitol Hill saw its first deadlock of the term on the Senate floor this morning.
辩论的结果两边不相上下
The hotly contested energy bill ended up in a 50-50 tie.
这意味着副总统 莱娜斯的那一票是最关键的
That means it will now be up to Vice President Reynolds to cast the deciding vote.
我知道自己像个破掉的留声机 但你工作太努力了
I know I sound like a broken record, but you work too hard.
你应该多去外面玩儿 拉上一帮朋友什么的
You need to get out, hang out with your friends more.
男人怎么样?
What about men?
如果这是你对我社交的看法 我一定会很凄惨
If this is your exposé on my social life, it's about to be a real sad one.
我 恩... 我一碰到恋爱的事 就走霉运
I... I've had some bad luck when it comes to relationships.
是运气差还是男孩子太坏了?
You had bad luck or you had bad boys?
我想我两者都有
I think I've managed to have a little of both.
是的 你说得没错 我就没打算找个好男孩
Yeah, you know, you're right. I don't tend to go for the nice guys.
我喜欢那种内心深藏不露的家伙
I like the ones with the deep-seated emotional issues
我可以改造他们 然后变成我自己的
I can internalize and make my own.
-比如说斯科菲尔德?  -不 不是斯科菲尔德那种
-Mmm-hmm. Like Scofield?  -Nope, not like Scofield.
别骗人了 每次他来你那儿打针
Don't lie to me. Every time he comes in for his shot,
你要花上20分钟帮他卷袖子
you spend 20 minutes rolling up his sleeve.
知道吗? 他确实很有意思
You know what? I think he's interesting.
而且很有魅力 但他仍是个囚犯
And I think he's attractive, but he's still an inmate.
我可以向你保证
I can promise you one thing.
你绝对不会看到 我和一个囚犯擦出火花
And that's that you will never see anything happen between me and an inmate.
迈克尔
Michael.
什么?你说什么?
What? What'd you say?
我倾注了所有心血
I put my blood into this.
站住!站住别动!跪下!
Stop! Freeze right there! Get down on your knees!
请别开枪!
Please don't shoot! Don't shoot!
伊利诺伊州的法律对企图逃跑的犯人并不怎么仁慈的
You know the state of Illinois doesn't look too kindly upon prisoners who try to escape.
被指控的话 你会被送回县监狱呆上三个月
Charges are filed, you get sent back to county for three months.
回来的时候已经又多了10年刑期了
Come back here with 10 more years added to your bid.
我不是想逃跑
I wasn't trying to escape.
你当然不想
Sure you weren't.
你只是在那儿对着月亮凄叹
You were just out there howling at the moon.
如果我是你 我就招供了 墨西哥佬
If I were you, I'd better start talking, mano.
我今天一直呆在那院子里
I stayed out after yard today.
我在露天看台地下呆到了天黑
I waited under the bleachers until it got dark.
有人会从墙外面扔东西进来
Something was gonna come over the walls.
吸毒和逃跑一样是重罪
Drugs is almost as bad as escape.
上次有个家伙在墙边搞海洛因 被多加了5年徒刑
Last guy had heroin slingshot over the wall got a nickel added to his bid.
我不是为了毒品
It wasn't drugs.
那他妈的到底是什么?!
Then what the hell was it?
搜身!
Frisk him!
看我们找到了什么?
What do we have here?
花内裤?
A pair of grunds?
你冒着被关单独禁闭的危险去搞内裤?
You risked going to the SHU for a pair of grunds?
妈的 你冒着被增加刑期的危险
Hell, you risked adding extra time to your bid,
去搞内裤?
all for a pair of panties?
我女友只是想让我知道 她在想我 老大
My girl just wanted me to know she was thinking about me, boss
你的手真是不听使唤啊 不是么?
You got a real beefer on your hands, don't you?
我知道 老大 这是我做过的最蠢的事
I know, boss. It's the dumbest thing I've ever done.
我害怕我在这里呆得太久 她就不要我了
I'm just scared that being here, I'm gonna lose her.
-他是为了爱情  -那么说你理解我了
-He did it for love.  -Then you understand.
是啊 当然 苏克雷 我理解你
Yeah, sure, Sucre. I understand.
你以后别栽到我手上
Don't let me catch you alone next time, okay?
苏克雷!
Sucre!
水缸?
Sink?
苏克雷
Sucre.
-迈克尔在哪?  -你的另一边
-Where's Michael?  -Other side of you.
迈克尔 迈克尔!
Michael! Michael!
迈克尔!
Michael!
迈克尔 快
Michael, come on.
警卫!
Badge!
怎么了?
Yeah?
你去看一下我兄弟 他没反应了
Check out my brother. He's not responding.
什么?
What?
斯科菲尔德 去查看一下 他毫无反应 拜托了
Scofield. Check him out.He's not responding. Please.
斯科菲尔德 斯科菲尔德
Scofield. Scofield.
12号牢房需要医生
I need a medic in 12 now.
-12号牢房需要医生 重复 快  -什么?
-I need a medic in 12 now. I repeat, now.  -What?
第八大道有电器商店 弄好他的手机
There's an electronics store on Eighth Avenue. Grab his phone.
我们十分钟就回来 你呆在沙发上
We'll be back in 10 minutes. Stay on the couch.
你已经接通了欧文· 克雷唯克 我现在无法接听电话
Hi, you've reached Owen Kravecki. I can't come to the phone right now.
你真地以为你按四个键 比我按一个要快?
You really think you're gonna get to four buttons before I get to one?
请留言 我会回电话的
Leave a message, and I'll return your call.
谢谢 祝你愉快!
Thanks. Have a great day.
12号开灯
Light on 12.
麻烦你在外面等 好吗?
Would you wait outside, please?
迈克尔?
Michael?
好 让我摸摸你的手腕
Okay, you're going to feel my fingers on your wrist.
来 我得看一下你的眼睛
Come on, I need your eyes.
我要看一下那只手
I'm going to take a look at that hand.
你会没事的
You're going to be okay.
-苏克雷被...  -我听说了
-Sucre got...  -I heard.
希望他已经把事情做好了
Papi better had did us right, man.
希望他时间足够
Hope he had enough time.
我们很快就可以知道了
Looks like we're about to find out.
动作快点
Make it fast.
我还以为我们选择 林肯·布伦斯作为替罪羊
I thought we picked Lincoln Burrows off the street
是因为他是个无法保护自己的社会下层人士
because he was some lowlife who couldn't defend himself.
现在我才发现 原来他父亲
Now I learn it's all about his father,
是公司一直想了却旧恩怨的间谍?
some old spook that the Company's trying to settle a score with?
幸运的是
Well, fortunately for us,
公司的议程和我们的议程 最后是会达成一致的
the Company's agenda and our agenda have the same endgame.
卡罗琳 这行我已经干了15年了
Caroline, I've been doing this for 15 years,
一直以来 事情都是关于你
and it's never been about anything other than you,
你的家庭 最重要的是 关于这个国家
your family, and most importantly, this country.
我现在需要知道我到底为谁效力
Now, I need to know who I'm working for here.
-你为我效力  -向我保证
-You are working for me.  -Promise me that.
我向你保证 保罗 我得挂了
I promise you, Paul. I got to go now.
我又有幸做些什么呢
And to what do I owe this honor?
今天下午的参议院投票
To the vote on the Senate floor this afternoon.
听着 我明白 否决权在我手里 我投否决票 就这样
Look, I get it. The vote comes down to me, I vote "no." Lt'll get done.
事实上 这次我们需要你投赞成票
Well, actually, we are going to need you to vote "yes" on this one.
我要确定我是不是听清楚了
I want to make sure I heard you straight.
你要我投环保论者的票?
You want me to vote on the environmentalists' side?
这个投票没关系
This isn't about a vote.
这是有关你和你在选民心中印象的问题
This is about you and how you look to voters.
现在 我们的国家变得日益需要多样化的能源
Now, we have a nation that is growing increasingly hungry for alternate energy.
如果你这次再保持中立
So if you come across as more centrist,
你就会获得更多人的支持
you'll appeal to the broader swath of the electorate,
明年你就很可能当选
the very people who will get you elected next year.
再说 一旦议案到了总统那儿 他一定一票否决
Besides, once that bill hits the President's desk, he'll veto it.
那样 我们就得到我们所有想要的了
Then we'll get precisely what we always wanted anyway, won't we?
你是不是连毛都没长全?
You probably don't have a hair on your body, do you?
滚你的王八蛋
Just back your punk ass up.
嘿 颓纳!快过来
Hey, Tweener! Get over here.
看来艾弗卡托是看上你了
Looks like Avocado has taken a shine to you.
如果你想做他狱友我可以成全你
I could set you up as cellies if you want.
不要这么说 好吗?
Stop it, all right?
我这次探听到点消息
I got something for you this time.
斯科菲尔德那帮家伙 他们在策划着什么事
Scofield and his boys, they're up to something.
能不能具体一点?
How about being a little more specific?
不管是什么 好像和他们修的那个房间有关...
Whatever it is, it's got to do with that room they're fixing.
和那地毯有关
Something to do with the carpet.
让我一下 伙计
Excuse me, fellas.
滚开!
Out of the way!
迈克尔!
Michael!
迈克尔! 迈克尔!
Michael! Michael!
完全没有反应 给他注射镇静剂
He's totally non-responsive, so start him on chlorpromazine.
我觉得他有间歇精神病发作
And I believe he's in danger of a psychotic break.
一旦他精神病发作 你就立马通知我
I want you to notify me immediately if and when that happens.
把他清理干净
Clean him up.
你吓我一跳
You scared me.
把枪放下 你不会杀人
Put it down. You're not a killer.
你不想行事这么草率吧
You don't want to make any rash mistakes here, LJ.
别动!
Don't move!
-冷静 冷静...  -闭嘴!
-Go easy, go easy...  -Shut up!
LJ 解决问题有其它方法的 好吗?
LJ, there's other ways out of this, you know, okay?
我可以帮助你的 但如果你扣下扳机
I can help you beat this rap, but if you pull that trigger,
那你就真的成了杀人犯 我就帮不了你了 懂吗?
you really will be a killer, and then I can't help you, okay?
我是政府部门的 LJ 我能帮你办到很多事
I'm government, LJ. There's a lot of things I can do for you.
你能帮我的唯一一件事就是去死!
The only thing you can do for me is die!
放下武器!
Drop your weapon!
我说了 放下武器!
I said drop your weapon!
看来你只能以后再动手了 哈?
Guess you're going to have to take a rain check on that one, huh?
放下武器!
Drop the gun now!
别 我按你说的做了
No. I did what you said.
你废话一大堆 那边根本什么都没有
You brought me a pile of crap. There was nothing there.
我们慢慢来 伙计 多给我点时间
Boss, come on, man. I just need some more time.
我已经给你时间了 你简直是在浪费我的时间
You had your time. You're a waste of my fries.
打开88号门!
Open on 88!
能不能再给我次机会
Dude, just give me another try.
88号门关上!
Close on 88!
别想了
Have at it.
老大
Boss.
老大!
Boss!
你挺走运
You're lucky.
这孩子身上有两桩命案了
Kid's got a warrant for double homicide.
哦 天 开玩笑吧?
Oh, dear. Are you serious?
你之前有和他联系吗?
Did you have any prior contact with him?
知道他为什么选择你家吗?
Any idea why he chose your house?
不清楚 他不停的叫喊"你杀了我妈妈"
I mean, he was screaming something like, "You killed my mom,"
还说我是什么政府特工什么的...
and going on about me being a government agent, and...
我不知道 大概这孩子吸过毒了吧
I don't know, it just seemed like that kid was on drugs or something.
你以什么为生 克雷唯克先生?
What do you do for a living, Mr. Kravecki?
我是一个脱水肉类的区销售经理
I'm a regional sales manager for a dehydrated meat distributor.
什么 你是说牛肉干之类的?
What, you mean like jerky?
-是的 你爱吃?  -什么种类的?
-Yes. you a fan?  -What kind?
美洲野牛
Buffalo.
拿些去 真的 我这儿全是这东西
Have some. Really. I'm swimming in the stuff.
一小时后吃午饭
One hour till lunch.
-出了什么问题?  -就是你所看到的
-So, what's the problem?  -You're looking at it.
-什么 铁网旁边的那个?  -是的 他是我的新狱友
-What, Haywire?  -Yep. He's my new cellmate.
我想我得了双重性格的精神紊乱
They think I have schizoaffective disorder with bipolar tendencies.
-你的纹身  -纹身怎么了?
-Your tattoos.  -What about them?
-他们是什么?  -只是纹身而已
-What are they of?  -They're just tattoos.
这家伙的皮肤上有个迷宫
The man's got a maze on his skin.
他为什么那么做? 他为什么在皮肤上弄个迷宫?
Why would he do that? Why would he put a maze on his skin?
是个通道 通向哪里的?
It's a pathway. Where does it lead?
好啊 朋友 你说得没错
Hello, roomie. You were right about my tattoo.
那确实是通道 和你想得一样
It is a path, just like you thought.
我需要你回忆一下 朋友
And I need you to remember when you saw it, Haywire.
回忆一下那通道是怎么样的
I need you to remember what it looked like.
你觉得你能做到吗?
Do you think you can do that for me?
你是谁?
Who are you?